<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>Plugin suggest</title>
    </properties>
    <body>
        <section name="Plugin suggest">
            <subsection name="Introduction">
                <p>
                    The Suggest plugin allows users to submit ideas, proposals or questions for submitting to votes
                    and comments from visitors. It allows for public consultations and discussion forums.
                </p>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name = "Main Features">
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Dynamically creates a content type that can be submitted by users.
                        A content type is created by selecting the different fields that should be
                        provided by the user when submitting a proposal.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Management of the content deposited by the users (publication, publication, deletion of certain proposals and comments).
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Ability to filter proposals by date of publication, category or by means of a search field.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        Possibility to order proposals by popularity or chronological order.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name = "Authentication Management">
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        Ability to require the user to be authenticated in order to vote, comment or submit a proposal. 
                    </li>
                    <li> Ability to prevent a user from voting multiple times for the same proposal. </li>
                </ul>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name = "Moderation of content submitted by users">
                <ul>
                    <li> Ability to require proposals and comments to be published only after verification by the moderator (s) of the sugg. </li>
                    <li> Send email notification when submitting a proposal, comment or report of a proposal considered inadequate </li>
                </ul>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name = "Other Features">
                <ul>
                    <li> Enabling / disabling a suggest with an unavailable message. </li>
                    <li> Consultation of proposals and comments with possibility of export. </li>
                    <li> Control of user input by regular expressions. </li>
                    <li> Ability to add a Captcha in the proposal entry form.
                        (I.e available by the addition of a Captcha) </li>
                    <li> Managing regular expressions, managing export xsl, managing categories ... </li>
                </ul>
            </subsection>
        </section>
    </body>
</document>